(Sheldon:)well, then,
I will happily catch them
(Sheldon:)with the reproductive sac
on my upper flermin.
(Sheldon:)I'm not the best
at reading facial cues,
(Sheldon:)but I can see that
you're a little turned on.
(Leonard:)You know, if you're not
gonna learn how to do this,
(Leonard:)they make some
pretty good clip-ons.
(Sheldon:)Bruce Wayne doesn't
wear a clip-on.
(Leonard:)Bruce Wayne doesn't make
his roommate tie it for him.
(Sheldon:)His name is Alfred,
and, yes, he does.
(Leonard:)There, perfect.
(Sheldon:)What, are you sure?
(Sheldon:)It's my first prom,
I want to do it correctly.
(Leonard:)I thought you were gonna
pretend to be an alien.
(Sheldon:)I was, but Penny didn't want to.
(Sheldon:)You didn't want to.
(Sheldon:)Bernadette, Amy, Koothrappali
and Wolowitz didn't want to.
(Sheldon:)And even I knew it was weird
to hire somebody.
(Leonard:)Was that a flask?